A Guide to the William Ingham Papers, 1945-2013: SC 0002
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 2: Teaching and Coursework, 1960-2013
  - 2.1: Courses, 1960-2013
    - P430 Chemical Potentials, gen'l conditions for equilibrium & stability phase & chemical equilibria, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - P430 Jacobians, 1982, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - P430 Statistics of Identical Particles, 1983, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - P430 Lecture Notes, 1977-1985, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Handout: Velocity Dist'n, 1983, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - P445 Hour Tests, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - P445, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - E & M Lecture Notes, 1987-1989, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - E & M Final Exams, 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - P460/560 Quantum Mechanics Problem Sets, Spring 1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - P460/560 Quantum Mechanics Hour Test & Final Exams, 1979-1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - P460,560 Spherical Harmonics, 1980, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - P460, P560 QM notes & handouts: Gaussian Wave Packet, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - P460, 1984, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Physics 460 (Folder 1 of 2), 2001-2002, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Physics 460 (Folder 2 of 2), 2001-2002, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - P460 Quantum Mechanics, 2002, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Phys 4160, TuTh 8-9:15 in Miller 120, Spring 2005 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Physics 460, 2005, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - P460, 2005, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - P460, 2005-2010, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - P470 HT's and Final, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Phys 470 Use of Manifestly Invariant Dfins. For frad. Div. curl., Spring 1986 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Continuum Mechanics P470 Lecture Notes, 1986, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Phys 480 Notes 1983 (Folder 1 of 2), 1972-1984, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Phys 480 Notes 1983 (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1984, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Physics 480, 1989, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Phys 480 Homework, 1992, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - P480, 1992, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - P480-Astro., 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Ellipses P480, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Phys 480 2003 (Folder 1 of 2), 2003, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Phys 480 2003 (Folder 2 of 2), 2003, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Phys 480 '05 Pt 1, 2004-2007, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Phys 480 '05 Pt 2, 2007, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Phys 480- Spring 2005 MWF 11:15-12:05 Miller 120, 2003-2005, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Phys 480, 1992-2007, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - P480 (Astrophysics)- Sp. 2007 MWF 12:20-1:10 P&C 2116, 2006-2007, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - P480 2007, 2003-2007, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Phys 480/580 Lecture Notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Phys 497: Topics: GR Fall 2005, 2005-2008 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Phys 497- QM3 TuTh 11-12:15, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Stockhauser P498 F'80 High Magnetic Fields, 1976-1980, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - P520 Lect. Notes Sp '85, 1960-1985, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Mechanics: Spring '85 P520, 1985, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Phys 520 Classical Mechanics Hour Tests & Final Exams, 1979-1985 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - P560-Spring 1979, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Phys 560 Quantum Mechanics Homework, Spring 1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Phys 560, Lecture Notes, Spring 1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Phys 560: Spring 1980, 1980, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Physics 580- Fall 1977-82, 1977-1982, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Phys 580-Cosmology Notes, 1982-1984, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Phys 580 Homework: Sp 1982-84 (Folder 1 of 2), 1977-1984, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Phys 580 Homework: Sp 1982-84 (Folder 2 of 2), 1977-1984, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Phys 580 1979, 1979-1992, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - P580 Notes: Sp'84 (Masters), 1977-1984, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Astrophysics: Brief Notes & Xeroxes 1982, 1968-1983, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Astrophysics, 1989, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Astr. 120, 2009, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Astr. 120, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Astr. 121 Test, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Astr. 121, 2011, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Astr. 121, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Astr. 121 (Folder 1 of 2), 2013, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Astr. 121 (Folder 2 of 2), 2013, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Astr 121-001 (TuTh8), 2013, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Bio 490, 2002, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Chem 341 Organic Chem, 1985, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Chem 432-DeGraff, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - CS 448-49, 1984-1985, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Masters for Calorimetry Lab, 1994, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Lunar Observations (UMSC), undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - UMSC 101 Bright Ideas, 1993, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - UMSC 101 Overheads, 1993, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - UMSC 101 Tests, 1994-1996, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - UMSC 101- academics sequences, 1994-1995, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - UMSC 101, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - UMSC 101 Transparencies, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - HON 200C, 1989, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Honors 300F and 200C, 1982-1992, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Honors 300F, 1982-1986, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Honors 300F, 1983-1986 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - HON 300K Readings, 1986-1988, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - HON 300F Handouts, 1987, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Honors 300K, Rathiens: "The Consequences of Nuclear War", undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - HON 300K, 1987-1989 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - HON 300M: Women in Science, 1999-2000, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - HON 300Z Final Exam, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Honors Course Background, 1986-1987, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Honors 301, Fall 2009, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - M135 Trig Transcendence, 1987-1988, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Math 235, 2009-2012, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Math/CS 248 Fall '82, 1982, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Math 248 Notes & Assignment, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Math 267E: Intro. To Acoustics, 2003-2005, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Math 341, 2011-2013, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Math 341, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - MP 365: Spring 2000 (CFD), 2000 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Gender, Class, and Science, 2000-2007, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Women in Physics, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Women in Science and Technology, 2000-2002, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - As They Are, 1991-1992, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Freshman Seminar Reader Articles, 1975, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - GSCI 121, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - GSCI 121: Physics of Light & Sound Manual, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - GSCI 121, Old Tests, (Folder 1 of 2), 2006-2008, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - GSCI 121, Old Tests, (Folder 2 of 2), 2006-2008, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - GSCI 121, Spring 2007 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - GSCI 121: Physical Nature of Light & Sound Lectures, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - GSCI 121: PowerPoint Slides, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - GSCI 121- 0004 (Spring 2007), 2007, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - GSCI 121- Summer 2007, 2007, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - GSCI 121 Lecture, 2007, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - GSCI 121, Study Questions, 2007, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - GSCI 121 Outline, 2009-2010, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - GSCI 121- May '08, 2008, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - GSCI 121- Spring 2008, 2008, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - GSCI 121 Review Sheets, 2008, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - GSCI 121 Background, 2008, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - GSCI 121, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - GSCI 163-164 Labs, 2006, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - GSCI 163-0302 Sp. 2006, 2006, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - GSCI 163-164 (Folder 1 of 2), 2009-2010, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - GSCI 163-164 (Folder 2 of 2), 2009-2010, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - GSCI 163-164 Sp 2010, 2009-2010, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - GSCI 163 Lab, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - LS 101 Final Exam Spring 1994, 1992-1994, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Readings for LS 101 Connections, Fall 1992 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Readings for LS 101, Education as Liberation or Training 1992, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Readings for LS 101 1992, The Individual in the Social Context, 1992-1994 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Readings, LS 101 Origins & Deities '92, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - LS 101 Readings, Education as Liberation or Training 1994, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Readings, LS 101 The Individual in the Social Context, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Readings, LS 101 Origins & Deities, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - LS300 Sci Biblios & Background Notes, 1991, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - LS300: Hour Tests & Finals, 1991-1993 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - LS300, 1991-1993, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - LS300, Reader in the 20th Century Science, 1992-1993, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - LS300 Text Files 1992, 1992, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - LS300/300H: MWF 2PM Sp '93, 1983-1993, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Hist 324: Spring 2000 History of Western Science, 1998-2001, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Hist 324 Reading Guides 07, 01, 1997-2001, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Hist 324- Spring 2001 MWF 11:15-12:05 Jackson 1A, 2000-2001, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Hist 324- Materials, 2001, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Hist 324-Spring 2011 Stockpile, 2001, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Hist 324 2001, 1997-2001, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Hist 324- Fall '98, 1998-2001, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Hist 324, Fall 1997 (Folder 1 of 2), 1997, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Hist 324, Fall 1997 (Folder 2 of 2), 1997, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - History 324, 1995-1998, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Hist 324 (Folder 1 of 2), 1998-2005, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Hist 324 (Folder 2 of 2), 1998-2005, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Hist 325 Syllabus, 1992-1995, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - HIS 328-329, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Hist 328- Spring 2003 MWF 12:20-1:10 Miller 120, 2001-2007, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Hist 328 2003 (Folder 1 of 2), 1992-2008, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Hist 328 2003 (Folder 2 of 2), 1992-2008, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Hist 328 (Folder 1 of 2), 2003-2008, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Hist 328 (Folder 2 of 2), 2003-2008, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Hist 328 2003, 1989-2003, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Hist 328 Research 2003 (Folder 1 of 2), 2003, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Hist 328 Research 2003 (Folder 2 of 2), 2003, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - HIS 328 Spring 2003 Teaching Plus Newspaper/ Web Clippings, 1991-2003, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - History of Science 328, 2004, 1971-2004, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Hist 328, 2005, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Hist 328 Biographies, 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Hist 328 History of Science Notes: Reading Guides, 1997-2003, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - HIS 328-Spring 2008, 2008, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Hist 328 Tests, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Hist 329 Proposal & Sources, 1971-2003, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Hist 329 (Folder 1 of 2), 2003-2006, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Hist 329 (Folder 2 of 2), 2003-2006, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Hist 329 Material, 2004, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Hist 329: Spring 2004, 2004, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Hist 329 Test, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Hist 329 (Folder 1 of 2), 2006, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Hist 329 (Folder 2 of 2), 2006, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Fall 2006 Hist 329, 2006, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Hist 329 Course Evaluations, Fall 2006, 2006-2007 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Hist 329 (Folder 1 of 2), 2006-2007, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Hist 329 (Folder 2 of 2), 2006-2007, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Hist 329, Kevles Q's (already handed), undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - 2.2: General Teaching, 1972-2013
    - Abundances of Common Elements, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Appendix 1.D: A Sense of Scale, 1982, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Assorted Transparencies, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Assorted Wikipedia Articles, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Atomic/Nuclear Chronology, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Chronology of Evolution & Historical Events, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Coding Material Inside a Thermos Bottle, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Computer Applications Background, 1978-1987 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Computing in Advanced Undergraduate Physics, 1991-2007 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Constellation Maps 1972-1973, undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Cosmology Lecture 1974.0219, 1973-1974, undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Cosmology Transparencies, undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Daily Schedules, undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Electrostatics, 1986-1987, undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Elem Abs, 1984-1994, undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Exploring Black Holes Solutions Manual, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Exploring Black Holes, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Exploring Black Holes, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Exploring Black Holes, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Wheeler & Bertschinger's Exploring Black Holes, JMU Departmental Office Copy, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Wheeler & Bertschinger's Exploring Black Holes, Fall 2008 marked up copy, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Taylor, Wheeler & Bertschinger's Exploring Black Holes, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Film notes, 1994-2003 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Forms, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Formula Sheets P/30, 1994-1998, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - General Physics Problems; Thermal Physics, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Grids: Paper, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Handouts, 1979-1987, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Hist/Bio/Phil of Sci, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - History Trans Masters, 1991-2003 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Idea for Visuals, 1993-1994, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Illustration guides, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Instructor's Solutions Manual to accompany An Introduction to Thermal Physics, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Instructor's Manual for Kreyszig's Advanced Engineering Mathematics (15th ed.), 1987 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Introduction to Vector Diff Operator "DEL", 1981-1982, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Liboff Problem Solns, Ch. 1-5, 2009-2010, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Limits to Growth, 1972, undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Maps and Charts: Personal, 1985, undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Maps: Originals and Transparencies, undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - MATLAB exercises, undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Handouts/Papers, 2011, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Test Keys, handouts & syllabi, 1981-2009 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Modern Physics, 1980-1982 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Other E & M Exercises, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Periodic Table 3/82, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Physics Course Offerings, 2005-2008 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Physics Informal Guidebook, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Physics Solutions Manual 2005, 2005, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - PowerPoint Slides, 2008, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Prepared transparencies, undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Problems & Solutions, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Reference Sheets, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Reference Sheets, 1983-1993, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Relativity Reference Sheets, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Scales in the Universe, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Scales of Size and Distance, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Scales of Size & History: Masters, 1985, undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Scales of Size, Distance, & Time, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Seating Charts, undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - A sense of Scale ca. 8/82, 1982, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Slide Notes JB, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Special Scale Papers, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Special Scales and 1-2-5-10 Paper, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Strogatz Exercises (Folder 1 of 2), 2013, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Strogatz Exercises (Folder 2 of 2), 2013, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Student Evaluations Thru Su 95, 1991-1995, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Symon Problems & Solutions, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Tables, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Teaching Blips, 1990, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Teaching S7chedules, 1976-1995 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Toolboxes:1.1-1.3, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Transparencies in Flight, 1997-2002, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Wishlist, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Xeroxes & Notes: CosPer, 1982-1983, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Series 3: Research and Scholarship, 1945-2013
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series consists mostly of scholarly articles and handwritten notes by Dr. Ingham pertaining to his scholarly pursuits, some of which are not directly related to physics. Many of these scholarly articles have dates handwritten in the top left corner of the page, which indicate when he actually printed or used these articles. If no date was written on them, then the date of publication is used for description purposes. This series also contains correspondence between Ingham and various scholars about their work, such as edits for textbooks and book reviews. Dr. Ingham conducted much research on James Madison and the sciences; related documentation is included. Large collections of Wikipedia and other web page printouts were removed and given back to the donor.
  - 20th Century Physics Timelines (1881-1955), undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - 3C 345, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - A0620-00 paper, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - AAPT Publications, 1987-1990 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - AAPT, Strategic Programs for Innovations in Undergraduate Physics: Project Report, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - About Brachistochrones and Catenaries Notes, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - About Brachistochrones and Catenaries Transparencies, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Aeronautics Figures (Tennekes, von Mises, Jones, et al), 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Adiabatic Sound Waves in a Uniform Fluid (Application: Doppler curve from a cruising airplane), 1999-2001 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Air Resistance on Various Objects From Bennett, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Airfoils & Aeronautics, 1999-2001 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Garland Allen. Life Science Biblio, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Alphabetical list of scientists through history, undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - American Eugenics Movement, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - American, Journal of Physics Q & A's, 1994-1997 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - American Institute of Physics, Degree Recipient Reports, 1994-2000 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - American Institute of Physics, Roster of Physics Departments with Enrollment and Degree Data, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Andrei Sakharov biography, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - An Apology for Modern Astronomy, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Appraisal: Science Books for Young People, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Articles on Interstellar Communication Plasma & Cosmology, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Articles on teaching Physics, 1969-1971 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - "The Articulate Traveler Johann Georg Kohl: Chronicler of American Continents," Library of Congress Exhibition, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Assorted Articles, 2005, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Articles, 2005-2006 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Articles & Notes, 1981-2008 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Atomic/Nuclear Chronology, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Atmospheric Structure and Chemistry, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Auden's "A New Year Greeting," Marples' "Life on the Human Skin," Updike's "The Dance of the Solids," Byard's "Poetic Responses to the Copernican Revolution", 1977, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Background Info for History of Science & LS 300, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Basic Governing Equations for Motion of a Nonrating Sphere Through a Fluid, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Batcheler Appendices, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Batcherlor's Tables of Fluid Properties, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Beowulf, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Bibliography on Arms Control & Defense, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Biophysics Notes & Articles, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - "Bittersweet Romance", 1973 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Black Holes & Cosmology, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Blips & Clips, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Bohr's "Natural Philosophy and Human Cultures," and Feynman's "Probability and Uncertainty", 1961, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Book Codes, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Booklist, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Booklists, 1987-2002 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Booklists, 2011-2012 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Booklists and acquisitions, 1993-1995 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Book wants, 1992-1995 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Book wants-individual, 1997-2003 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Books, 1985-1995 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Books & other sources: History & Philosophy of Science and Technology, 1971-1991 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Boorstin, Mason, & K. Jefferey History of Science Reading/Class Notes, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Boundary Layers, 2000-2001 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Brecher, Ingham, & Morrison "X-Ray Emission" reprints, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Brown, Pais, & Pippard's Twentieth Century Physics Vol. II, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Bulletin of the American Physical Society, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Vannevar Bush. Science: The Endless Frontier, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Catenaries, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Celestial Sphere Problems, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Centrifuge, 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Chandler Colloquium "Life in the Universe", 1978 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Chandlers Colloquium: The Challenge from Space Technology, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Charles Darwin in Article, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Chemical Elements March, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Chemical Engineering News, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Clayton and Reif Problems, 1970s (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Coin Weights, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Collected Readings Project, 1988-1991 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Colloquia & Notes (notebook), 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Colloquia & Notes (notebook), 1975 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Colloquia & Notes (notebook), 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Compound Optical Instruments, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Computational Constellation Overlays, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Computational Research, 1976-1980 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Computer Program Print-outs (rolled): Neutwind Gaushaus (2) 497-939 Gaushaus (3) 935-1112, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Computers & Constellations, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Constellation Charts, 1978-2007 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Constellation HP, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - David Cook correspondence, beta testing, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Corrections to Harre's "Great Scientific Experiments", 1981 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Dwayne Yancey, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Cosmic Perspectives draft, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Cosmic Perspectives Glossary, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Cosmic Perspectives Notebook, undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Cosmic Perspectives Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Cosmic Perspectives Outline, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Cosmic Perspectives Outline, undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Cosmic Perspectives Outline, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Cosmic Perspectives Preface & Ch. 1, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 14)